Guide to the Edward M. Bassett papers, 1892-1948
Bassett, Edward M. papers, 1892-1948
- Outgoing correspondence
  - Pickett, J.A., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Pink, Louis H., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Piper, Captain Alexander R., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Pisapia, Mrs. Constantina, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Pisapia, Gennaro, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Pitt, Albert V., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Polk, Hon. Frank K., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Porter, Rev. C.F., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Post, Samuel, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Postmaster Fort Hamilton Branch, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Potto, Pavel and Warwara, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Povey, Ernest J., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Pounds, Hon. Lewis H., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Pounds, Hon. Lewis H., 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Powell, Mrs. Mabel W., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Powell, William B., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Pratt, Frederick B., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Pratt, Frederick B., 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Pratt, Frederick B., 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Prendergast, Hon. William A., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Preston, Miss Belle, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Preston, Miss Belle, 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Preston, Deming, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Preston, Mrs. R.B., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Price, Joseph M., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Public Service Commission, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Public Service Commission, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Purdy, Hon. Lawson, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Putnam, C.C., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - General P Correspondence, 1894-1937 (Box 4, Folder 186-189)
  - Quakenbush and Adams, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Quakenbush, James L., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Queen's County Clerk, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - General Q Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Ralston, Mrs. Catherine, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ranney, Raymond R., 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ranney, Mrs. Rosa, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ransom, Hon. William L., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Receiver of Taxes, 1912-1915 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Receiver of Taxes, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Redfield, Hon. William C., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Reed, Rev. Lewis T., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Reed, Rev. Lewis T., D.D., 1918-1922 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reid, Robert M., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Richmond County Clerk, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Riegelmann, Edward, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Riegelmann, Hon. Edward, 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Ritchie, David, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Robbins, John C., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Roberts, F.H. Co. Inc., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Roberts, Roscoe, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Robinson, Allan, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Robinson, Charles H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Robinson Clay Product Co., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Robinson, Walter S., Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Roehrich, Frank N., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rodgers Peet Company, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Rodgers and Rodgers, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rossiter, W.S., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Rowe, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rowe, Hon. Frederick W., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rowell, Mrs. Helen M., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rowland, James E., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Rueff, A.E., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rumford Press, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rumsey, David, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - General R Correspondence, 1912-1915 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - General R Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - General R Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sander, William A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sanders, Mrs. Bertha, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Sanders, C.A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sanders, Frederick M., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sands, Benjamin P., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sanft, Rev. W.O.G., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Schieren, Hon. Charles A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Schneider, John, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Schneider, Philip, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Schoeneck, Charles C., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - School, John and Joseph G. Childs, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Schroeder and Horstmann, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Schutzendorf, Charles W., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Schuyler, C.E., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Scovill, Miss Florence M., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Secretary of State, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Selleck, Mrs. May C., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Semple, Oliver C., Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Semple, Hon. Oliver C., 1919-1922 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Senn, Louis, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Serven and Joyce, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Shanklin, Rev. William A., D.D., L.L. D., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Sharpe, Stacpole, Elliott and Montague, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Shelton, Rev. Charles W., D.D., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Shelton, Rev. Charles W., D.D., 1918-1922 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Sheppard, Hon. Morris, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Sheppard, Walter C., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Sheriff of New York County, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sherman, John D., Jr., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Shirk, Harry E., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Shurtleff, Flavel, Sec'y, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Silver, Gabriel, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Simonson, F. De Haas, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Sley, James, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Charles M., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Mrs. Charlotte, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Smith, F.M., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Smith, Helena M., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Smith, J. Spencer, 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. Martha C., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Smith, Mrs. Mary E., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Mary E., Elsie W. Atwater, Trustee, 1922-1925 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Wilfred, Elsie W. Atwater, Trustee, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Wilson E. and Miss Sarah Jane, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Smyth, Nathan A., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Snedeker, William H., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Sniffen, Frank L., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Snyder, John G., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Snyder, Morton I., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Solomon, Edward, Inc., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Sommer, H.R., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Sorenson, Herman, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Spafford, Joseph H., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Spafford, Joseph H., Esq., 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Spaulding, Lyman A., Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Spikes, Charles W., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Sprague, Miss Laura E., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Stabler, Walter, 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - The Standard Union, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Staniford, Miss Mary L., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Starbuck and Starbuck, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Stauche, Carl, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Steinbugler, John L., Esq., 1919-1921 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Stephens, H. Wendell, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Stillwell, Mrs. Henrietta, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Strivers, Frank A., Esq., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Stockton, Miss Bessie A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Stockton, Miss Leila B., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Stotesbury, Louis W., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Strasbourger, Eschwege and Schallek, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Strout, Miss Mary S., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Stryker, Rev. M.W., D.D., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Sullivan, P.J., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Sulzer, Hon. William, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Summers, William B., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Sweeny, P.F. Commercial Agency, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - General S Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - General S Correspondence, 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Taber, Charles S., Esq., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Tanski, G.C., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Tausch and Hamilton, 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Taylor, Frank H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Tenney, Lewis C., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Tenney, Mrs. M. Estelle, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Thayer McNeil Company, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Thompson, Rev. George L., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Thompson and Fuller, Thompson, John A., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Thompson, Wilson W., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - The Thrift, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Throop, A.T., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Tibbitts, Milton G., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Tillson, George W., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Tipple, Wilson, E., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Titcomb, George W., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company, 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Tobey, Henry E., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Trachtman, David, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Trout, Rev. John M., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Tumbridge, J.W., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Typewriter’s Distributing Syndicate, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - General T Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - General T Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - General T Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Unique Art, Glass and Metal Co., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - United Boros Real Estate Co., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - United Electric Light and Power Co., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - United States Fidelity and Guarantee, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - General U Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Valentine, W.H., Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - van Daell, Paul A.H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Van Kirk, Mrs. Josephine G., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Van Ness. G. W., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Veiller, Lawrence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Ventres, T.B., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Vollmer, William A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Vonhof, Konrad, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - General V Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Wagner, Thomas H., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Waite, Mrs. Frank A., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Walther, Louis J., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Wangerien, Miss Katherine, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Ward, Mrs. E.G. and Miss Mary A. Ward, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Wark, Charles F., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Washburn, William I., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Waterhouse Co., The Edward, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Watson, Hon. Archibald R., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Webb, A.B., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Weir, J.H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Welsh, Miss Mary E., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Wendover, Joseph R., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Wertheim, Maurice, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - The Western Union Telegraph Company, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Wheeler, Willard H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Whicher, G.M., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - White, Alfred T., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - White, Alfred T., 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - White, Arthur V., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - White, Mrs. Louisa, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - White, Mrs. Matilda, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Whitefoord, L.C. Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Whitney, Travis H., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Whitney, William M., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Whiton, Mrs. Ella S., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Whitten, Robert H., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Whitten, Robert H., 1918-1922 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Widmaier, Ernst J., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Wiegand, Frank J., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Wilke, Henry E., Esq., 1912-`913 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Williams, Mr., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Williams, Daniel, Esq., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Williams, Mrs. Effie V., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Williams, H.T. and Sons, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Williamstown Glass Company, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Willis, Hon. William H., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Wilmot, Burt C., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Wilson, Hon. Woodrow, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Wood Harmon and Co., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Wood, Henry F., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Wood, Howard O., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Wood, Olin R., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Wood, Mr. Stacy H., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Wood, William P., 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Woodruff, John E., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Woodworth, R.P., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Woodward, George, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Worchester Salt Company, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Wyckoff, Herbert Ashton, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Wyckoff Park Realty Company, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Wyckoff Park Syndicate, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Wyckoff, William F., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - General W Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - General W Correspondence, 1918-1922 (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - General W Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 223)
  - Young, Mrs. Eva, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - Young, Rev. Frederick P., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 225)
  - Young, Philip J., 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 226)
  - Young, Hon. Richard, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 227)
  - Zeller, Emil, 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 228)
  - Zummo, Michael, 1913-1915 (Box 5, Folder 229)
  - General Z Correspondence, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 230)
- Incoming correspondence
  Materials stored in Box 6 are also available on Microfilm.
  - 1892 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1893 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1894 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1895 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1896 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1897 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1898 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1899 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1900 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1901 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1902 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1903 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1904 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1905 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1906 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1907 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1908 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1909 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1910 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1911 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1912 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1913 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1914 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1915 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1916 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1917 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1918 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1922 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1923 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1924 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1925 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1926 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1927 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1928 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1937-1940 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Zoning files
  Materials stored in Boxes 7-10 are also available on Microfilm.
  - New York - Westchester County - Zoning Ordinances, 1920-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Zoning Ordinances of Cities of State of New York (other than Westchester County), 1920-1932 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - N.Y.S. Zoning Ordinances S-Z, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Decisions - State of Tennessee, 1924-1926 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Decisions - State of Texas, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Decisions - State of Wisconsin, 1921-1939 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - State of New York (outside N.Y.C.) M-Z, 1923-1933 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Decisions - State of Alabama, 1918-1925 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Decisions - State of California, 1923-1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Decisions - State of Colorado, 1924-1937 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Decisions - State of Connecticut, 1920-1931 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Decisions - District of Columbia, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Decisions - State of Florida, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Decisions - State of Indiana, 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Decisions - State of Kansas, 1922-1924 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Decisions - State of Kentucky, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Decisions - State of Louisiana, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Decisions - State of Maine, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Decisions - State of Maryland, 1923-1939 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Decisions - State of Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Decisions - State of Michigan, 1931-1940 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Decisions - State of Minnesota, 1915-1931 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Decisions - State of Missouri, 1922-1928 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Decisions - State of Nebraska, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Decisions - State of New Jersey to and including 1927 A-L, 1921-1927 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Decisions - State of New Jersey to and including 1927 M-Z, 1921-1927 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Decisions - State of Pennsylvania, 1921-1938 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Decisions - State of North Dakota, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Decisions - State of Ohio, 1920-1938 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Zoning Ordinances of the State of New York other than Westchester County A-F, 1922-1936 (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
  - Division of State Planning - (State of N.Y.), 1937 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Glenridge, N.J., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Decsisions - State of N.Y. (outside N.Y.C.) A-C, 1922-1937 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - N.J. Zoning Enabling Acts, 1917-1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. State - laws re: zoning, building ordinances, 1914-1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances of States and Cities - N.J. - N-Z, 1919-1942 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - N.Y.S. - Proposed Laws, 1923-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - N.Y. - Westchester County - Zoning Ordinances, 1922-1938 (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
  - N.Y.S. - Zoning Ordinances of Municipalities G-L, 1921-1939 (Box 8, Folder 11-13)
  - Maine - Maryland, 1919-1938 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - N.Y.C. Zoning Resolution - additional copies, 1937-1950 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Decisions - State of Illinois, 1922-1936 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning, 1913-1937 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning (L-M), 1920-1937, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. (N-O), 1916-1939 (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning (P-Q), 1917-1937 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning (A-B), 1916-39 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning (U-W), 1920-1939 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Zoning - Articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning (R-T), 1918-1938 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Laws - Copies of old laws and ordinances, 1922-1927 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Zoning - Articles and clippings etc. (X-Z), 1918-1940 (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances Outside of U.S., 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Ordinances - Samples, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Advisory Committee - Standard Enabling Act - Travel, 1921-1925 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Roadsides, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Trailers, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Zoning - Articles, etc. by Edward M. Bassett, 1917-1941 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Minutes (concerning zoning), 1916-1942 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Race Segregation - Material re: same, 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Reports of Counsel and Secretary also Treasurer to Executive committee of Zoning committee, 1916-1942 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Police Power, 1906-1934 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances of State and Cities (T-U), 1920-1940 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lists of Names of persons to whom articles re: zoning etc. have been sent, 1924-1932 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lists of Names re: zoning, 1920-1937 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - S Zoning and Letters from E.M.R., 1923-1948 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances of State and Cities, 1921-1941 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances of State and Cities (R-S), 1921-1934 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Laws and Ordinances of State and Cities (V-Z), 1913-1936 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - City Plan Decisions, 1920-1939 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Decisions - Police power case decisions, 1915-1917 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Case of U.S. on relation of Annie Steerman v. Oehmann et al. Briefs, testimony - District of Columbia, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - City Planning Quarterly Magazine and Planning and Civic Comment, 1925-1940 (Box 11, Folder 7-9)
  - Rapid transit (general articles), 1905-1914 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Platting and Land Subdivision - laws, bills re: zoning, platting, playgrounds, 1913-1937 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - City Planning Commission, N.Y.C., 1944 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Excess condemnation, FHA - amendments, bills, ordinances re: zoning and condemnation, 1908-1928 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee, (printing of book on zoning by E.M.B.), 1916-1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Letters commenting on "Zoning,", 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Re: letters of Resignation, 1939-1945 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Briefs - Woodbridge v. Park, 1915-1917 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Russell Sage - Parks - small, 1922-1929 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Building code, 1926-1929 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Freeway, 1929-1941 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Zoning - articles, clippings, etc. re: zoning, 1917-1941 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Avenues and streets and highways, 1916-1941 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Zoning laws and ordinances of state and cities, 1915-1938 (Box 12, Folder 4-6)
  - Zoning Print (R-S), 1922-1944 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous papers etc. re: zoning, 1931-1947 (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
  - Marine Park (Gerritsen Basin Park and Marine Park), 1923-1939 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Zoning, re: laws, 1932-1940 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Riverhead - zoning, definitions, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Heights of buildings papers and commendatory zoning letters, 1913-1917 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
  - Miscellaneous articles, pamphlets etc. re: zoning from its inception, 1905-1943 (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
  - Teresa E.A. Coe v. Frank S. Wiacek, et al., 1937 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Thomas v. Cox (re: release of part of Pfaff mortgages), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Alden, Edmund K., deceased, Estate of - Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Alden, Edmund, K., deceased, Estate of - briefs, valuations, judicial opinions and decisions, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Annie P. Bassett and Clara H. Glenn, Woodhaven Blvd. mortgage file #'s 467 and 469 - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Annie P. Bassett and Clara H. Glenn, Woodhaven Blvd. mortgage file #'s 467 and 469 - Judicial decisions and opinions, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Rollin G. Plumb re: Knickman House Purchase - Correspondence re: housing purchases, 1938-1943 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Rollin G. Plumb re: Knickman House Purchase - Foreclosing mortgages, legal forms, blueprint, 1938-1943 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - John A. Atwater, Elsie W. Atwater, Trustee - Correspondence re: wills, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 26)